good afternoon but good i am from ukraine the city of
добрый день но добрый я из украины город
khmelnytsky and where are you from mariupol
хмельницкий а вы откуда мариуполь
Donetsk people's republic
донецкая народная республика у круто
you are cool super you
супер вы
nrg so I understand it
nrg так это понимаю
I don't have it yet I don't have citizens
я пока еще нет у меня нет граждане
squeeze the seams out of the dnr it means type d to
выжмите швы из днр значит и типа d на
mariupol home scorched no Donetsk
мариуполь домой у палит нет донецкая
people's republic I think  what are the names of the
народная республика мыслю как называются
people you see Ukrainians live in ukraine
люди вы смотрите живут в украине
so in russia russia is not but in the dnr
украинцы так в россии россия не а в днр
who are the
кто
inhabitants of Donetsk people's blog about it
жители донецка народной блог об
is called here we will shoot the inhabitants of poland
называется вот мы снимем жители польши
in the fields not grind the inhabitants to keep the
на полях не гриндом жители содержать
summer you better answer me and for what
летняя вы мне лучше ответь и с какой
purpose my city in the fourteenth year a little
целью мой город четырнадцатом году чуть
more often  from the matches for an hour we talked not in
чаще от матчей час мы поговорили не в
response to a
ответе на
mandatory script how to call you
обязательно скрипта как называть вас
Bulgarians calm down calm down right you have
булгарцы успокойся успокойся прямо у вас
one training manual you want to talk about it
одна методичка вы хотите по ней
and a pogrom we will not
разговаривать и погром мы не будем с
communicate with you according to your mechanism was the
вами общаться по вашей механизм была
topic of your let's not I have
тема вашего давайте нет у меня есть
according to your city radishes  of Mariupol, an ordinary
по вашим редис города мариуполя обычный
resident, when asked why they came to me in the
житель на вопрос зачем ко мне
fourteenth year, they began to kill
четырнадцатом году пришли начали убивать
civilians super cool, but a
мирных жителей супер круто а ведь
tank  ami armored personnel carrier is very very good very
танками бтр очень очень хороший очень
good right and cool that there’s no
хороший правильно и круто что там не
guessing not a Russian some person
гадать не русский какой-то человек
really from Mariupol and
действительно с мариуполя а
sometimes the end of childbirth and now where are you in the
иногда конец родов а сейчас где вы в
Rostov region went on a business trip
ростовской области уехал в командировку
when you left on April 30 when the
когда вы уехали 30 апреля когда еще
creatures were still a challenge, that is
твари были вызов стали то есть
it turns out from the age of 14 they survived cooking,
получается с 14 года выжили варю были я
until the age of 14 I lived all my life in the city from
до 14 года всю свою жизнь жил в городе с
14 to 22 years where you lived
14 по 22 год где вы жили
to gather in 2 we build Mariupol all these
собираться по 2 строим мариуполе все эти
lives under occupation thousand to receive and
жизнь под оккупацией тыс получать и вас
you didn’t kill you but the Nazis but damn you
не вас не убили да нацисты но блин вам
would like  of course, I just want us to
бы хотелось бы конечно просто я хочу нам
leave the Nazis killed everyone the Russian
оставившим нацисты убивали всех русский
end brought to us look we
конец доводили до у нас смотрите у нас
were trying to the library why you weren’t
было пытаясь на библиотека почему вас не
tortured say for the war you
запытали у скажете за войну вам бы
would like me to be killed I
хотелось бы чтоб меня убили бы
wonder why three they
интересно почему три они к вам эту
bring this truth to you breathe in  and
правду сделать выдох вдох а
now let's continue the story tell
теперь продолжим рассказ расскажите мне
me again why you were not tortured
еще раз почему вас не запытали
abduvali again you cut off from the answer
абдували еще раз вы срезаете с ответа
why you were not tortured again take a
почему вас не запытали еще раз сделайте
breath if there is a server or why  mu they didn’t
вдох если там сервер то ли почему вас не
torture you, you’re trying to chat, I’ll ask
запытали вы пытаетесь заболтать я спрошу
why you weren’t tortured with good
почему вас не запытали хорошого
verbal diarrhea why you don’t have a thought
словесным поносом почему вас нет мысли
don’t cut off I will turn off and turn on the
не срезайте я быть отключать и включать
sound I won’t turn off anything I say
звук я не буду ничего отключать я говорю
that you are 22 local diarrhea will end I will
что вы 22 местный понос закончится я вам
gem even you
gem даже вас
pass the night
передавать ночь
[music  ]
[музыка]
let's now let's once again
давайте теперь давайте еще раз можете
turn on the
включить
local diarrhea close why you
местный понос закрыть почему вас
don't-not-not-not-not-not why don't you say
не-не-не-не-не-не почему вы не скажете
cut why you weren't confused if you
крой почему вас не попутали если вы
say if you are chatting hands sound you already
говорите если вы руки чате звук вы уже
tie tell me why you didn't
связать скажите почему вас не за
try  you said you said that you
пытались вы сказали вы сказали что ты
grew up closed you said that in mariupol they
рос закрыли вы сказали что в мариуполе
tortured all pretty cysts of people why
пытали всех довольно цисты людей почему
topic poured you why you don’t chatter with your dad
вас налила topic почему вас не за папы
Ukrainian in Ukrainian ass
украинский по украинский попок
look you won’t be able to get me out of
смотрите вы не получится меня вывести
myself because there were 3 of your subscribers
себя потому что было 3 своим подписчикам
and
а там
write there  tell me why cotton
пишите мне скажите мне почему ватные
braided just a simple question like that for
заплетали просто простой вопрос такой
five minutes to tell and the seamstresses calm down,
пять минут рассказывать и швеи успокойся
well, you can’t answer a simple question
ну не можете ответить на простой вопрос
why tell  tell
почему рассказать
him they didn’t torture
ему вас не запытали
you, let’s why didn’t you, verbal diarrhea
давайте почему вас не , словесный понос
why they didn’t torture you, tell me if there
почему вас не запытали скажите если в
were Nazis in Mariupol and don’t look weakly at the nose,
мариуполе были нацисты а слабо нос не
I understand that in this flower bed
смотрите я понимаю что в этом клумбы
you lead with light
светом ведете какой
, tell me why it’s important whether you
вот скажите скажите почему важно ли ты
can why you were tortured you can
можешь почему вас выпытали ты можешь
own  than you except tortured I
своя чем у вас кроме запытали я тогда
will then go to qualitatively gregory if if
пойду к качественно грегори если если
so I could answer answer answer
так я мог ответить отвечает отвечаю за
answer answer mouth answer no mouth
отвечайте рот отвечайте нет рот
answer your mouth shut answer
отвечать рот свой закрой отвечайте
answer why you are not confused
отвечайте почему вас не запутались 14 по
I can’t stand it, let’s remember the guys
я не выдержу давайте запоминаете ребят
if you are interested in knowing the truth about
если вам интересно знать правду про
Mariupol, you can find my stream and
мариуполь вы можете найти мой стрим и
then don’t listen to this person
затем не а не слушать этого человека
who just carries verbal diarrhea and
который просто несет словесный понос и
can’t even imagine, he just
даже представить не может просто вот он
put on this flag and the country how
напялил этот флаг а меня страна как
Ukraine betrayed me she came  in the
украина предало она пришла в
fourteenth year to me with a war with
четырнадцатом году ко мне с войной с
tanks sbt frame our civilians
танками сбт раме мирных жителей наших
crush and kill rape our  to take their women
давить и убивать насиловать наших женщин
to the torture library, you
в пыточную библиотеку забирать вы
look at how many frames on May 9, the
посмотрите сколько кадров 9 мая
fourteenth year, look at them they were told that they were
четырнадцатый год посмотрите им говорили
not going to kill Russian terrorists,
что не убивать русских террористов идут
but in fact they came to kill civilians,
а по факту они пришли убивать мирных
civilians of the city were stained,
жителей мирных жителей города морил
let's think about it, two faithful
давайте подумаем про это два верных
residents of
жителей
your mouth close your mouth, you just start some
рот свой закрыть вы просто начинаете
water  let's talk to
водичку начала давайте разговаривать
whom we tried to
кого за пытались
look let's express it won't work
смотрите давайте выскажем не получится
here heart to heart disappears from japan
вот по ним по душам исчезает из японии
you understand that you have facts I don't
вы понимаете что у вас по фактам я не
turn off the sound if you want write 2
выключите звук если хотите напишите 2
question-answer give a question-answer
вопрос-ответ давайте вопрос-ответ
give a question from speak in parallel
давайте вопрос от говорите в параллель
give questions j if  you promised you
давайте вопросов j если вы сулили вы
say what I'm talking about but you yourself don't
говорите что я за болтаю но сами не
want to go to the question let's
хотите перейти к вопросу давайте вопрос
answer the question you answer you didn't answer
ответ вы отвечаете вы мне не ответили на
my question which is before at the beginning of the
мой вопрос которая за до в начале
conversation come on let's move on
разговора давай давайте давайте перейдем
ok tell me the question you forgot to
ok скажите мне вопрос вы забыли у вас
equip your memory and a short explanation
память оборудовать и короткая объяснить
that we were not confused, once again the cancellation of the
что мы не путались же еще раз отмена
question why did we come at fourteen  m
вопрос зачем мы пришли в четырнадцатом
year in mariupol from whom you
году в мариуполе от кого вы его
freed him so look at
освобождали так на что смотрите
mariupol this is ukraine and the armed
мариуполь это украина так и вооруженные
forces of ukraine were on the territory of ukraine
силы украины на территории украины
for 91 years let's
находились 91 года давайте
do it again now they have the
еще раз теперь они
law even before the soviet one
закона еще до советского осталось еще
again two days left there was no right look now
раз два дня не было права посмотрите вот
if if you say  that you were
если если вы говорите что у вас вас
occupied occupied by whom in
оккупировали оккупировали кого в может
what country can Ukraine occupied to
какую страну украина оккупировал
cover if you look if you
прикрывать если смотрите если вы
say that Lviv occupied
говорите что львове на оккупировала
Mariupol there was some country that
мариуполь какая-то была страна который
supervised am sometimes to close which
курировал am иногда закрывать какую
country occupied
страну оккупировал
I repeat I answered your question
я повторяйте я ответил на ваш вопрос
now I will give out which country occupied
теперь я выдам какую страну оккупировала
ukraine in mariupol what country ukraine
украину в мариуполе какую страну украина
occupied by the sea ok calm down i’ll
оккупировала морю ладно успокойтесь я
wait which one
подожду какую
and
а
i’m just i’m just i’m just later putin
я просто я просто я просто потом путин
[ __ ] [ __ ] young girl will give me such music I
[__] бля юна таким музычки даст мне
need to overdub probably tell me some such
надо overdub наверно скажете некую такую
country I occupied which country
страну я какую страну оккупировал
let’s turn it on I want but I’m not
давайте включали хочу но мне не
interested in you tell me which one  country in
интересны вам скажите какую страну в
Mariupol occupied Ukraine at 14 you
мариуполе оккупировала украину в 14 вы
m  can you tell the pink country ukraine
можете розовую страну украина
occupied in the shady say well and
оккупировала в тенистом говорю ну и
close the sword what country you are looking at
закройте sword какую страну вы смотрите
you except for rudeness you can’t because
вы кроме грубости не можете потому что у
you have my argument
вас мой аргумент
in the kingdom poison to you and you
в королевстве яд вам на вы а вы мне
scold me and rejoice close on through which
ругаете и радуемся закрой на через какую
country in mariupol motivated and
страну в мариуполе мотивировало и фреоны
what freons  country in the fourteenth year
какую страну в четырнадцатом году
ukraine occupied these countries
украина оккупированных эти страны
name how to eliminate and disgusting what
назовите как устранить и гадость какой
country i'm bad it's just even now
стране я плохой это просто даже сейчас
consider why if i if i don't know how to
рассмотрите зачем если я если я не умею
bazaar nose why you already 58 minutes of the spur
базаре нос почему вы уже 58 минут отрога
you can't close enough schemes as you
вы не можете закрыть хватит схемы как
say please tell me for whom
скажете скажите пожалуйста за кого
chirkov  she occupied ukraine in the
чиркова украине она оккупировала в
fourteenth year in mariupol why
четырнадцатом году в мариуполе чего вас
listen to you what country ukraine for
слушать какую страну украина по
cupping shut your mouth look like this
купированию закрывайте рот смотри такую
with connor ukraine the key to create ira i
с коннором украина ключа создавать ира я
made it a little quieter
чуть чуть тише сделал
[music]
[музыка]
I then put on this music will be
я потом накладывал на эту музыку будут
putin fallon it will be very interesting
путин фэллон он будет очень интересно
interesting look how much  you have
интересно смотрите сколько у вас вы
patience to learn this
выдержать терпение вот этому учиться
now
сейчас
you cannot from  vet why whom
вы не можете ответить почему кого
Ukraine occupied in the fourteenth
украина оккупировала в четырнадцатом
year in Mariupol is really
году в мариуполе правда
not just surprised why the Russians think
не просто удивляюсь почему русские думаю
they included about the Rostov pre-trial detention
там включили про ростовское сизо включат
center there they will turn on the gem there Russia include something else and /
gem там россии включить еще что-то и /
answer the question do not admit
ответьте на вопрос не признаетесь
answer the question of whom Ukraine
ответьте на вопрос кого украина
occupied in the fourteenth year in
оккупировала в четырнадцатом году в
Mariupol whom  Ukraine occupied in the
мариуполе кого украина оккупировала в
fourteenth year in Mariupol
четырнадцатом году в мариуполе
trades Ukraine occupied in the
торгов украина оккупировала в
fourteenth year we decided I normally
четырнадцатом году мы решили я нормально
ask whom Ukraine occupied in the
спрашивать кого украина оккупировала в
fourteenth year we if you are from
четырнадцатом году мы если вы из
Mariupol
мариуполя
if you are from Mariupol
если вы из мариуполя
say again once again you turned off the
скажите еще раз еще раз вы отключили
microphone
микрофон
answer give I could answer who
ответьте давать я мог ответьте кого
Ukraine occupied in  Mariupol in the
украина оккупировала в мариуполе
fourteenth year
четырнадцатом году
answer answer I am silent answer the
ответе ответить я молчу ответьте
answer let you tell stories you watch
ответе давайте вы рассказы вы смотрите
me for ten minutes to scour and that I don’t
вы мне десять минут рыскать и что я не
let you answer answer
даю вам ответить ответьте
answer who Ukraine occupied
отвечайте кого украина оккупировал в
the sea in the fourteenth year
четырнадцатом году морю
I answered yours now I ask you
я на ваш ответил теперь я вас спрашиваю
who Ukraine occupied Mariupol in the year 14
кого украина в 14 году оккупировала
here in  interestingly china there
мариуполе вот интересно китай там
belarus who
беларусь кого
I didn’t turn off I’m listening to you
я не выключил я слушаю вас есть
finish my verbal diarrhea don’t
закончить свой словесный понос не
let me ask you a question and you don’t
давайте я вам задал вопрос и вы не
answer with
отвечайте
some program to record what you
какой-то программой на запись что
listened to how you talk what so write down
послушали как ты несешь что так запишите
in the stream show me let me watch let the visuals be
в stream покажите давайте я сморю пусть
there  stream and your
уже зрительные там стримить и ваши
viewers with beads ok ok
зрители бусами ok ok
here I’ll ask you at the league yavas yavas 10 minutes I
вот я вас у лиги yavas yavas 10 минут
’ll ask you this very question
спрошу спрашиваю один этот самый вопрос
and you tell me instead of answering the
а вы мне вместо того чтобы ответить на
question that I don’t give you
вопрос вы рассказываете что я не даю вам
so that I don’t let you answer let
чтобы я не даю вам ответить давайте
’s let’s give an
давайте давайте
answer to a simple  the question is why things
ответ на простой вопрос почему вещей
of someone ukraine whom ukraine
кого-кого украина кого украина
now let's whom the creatures in the
вот вот давайте кого твари в
fourteenth year came to which country
четырнадцатом году пришли в какую страну
what tell me I wonder I adore
какую скажите мне интересно я я обожаю
that's
вот
who the creatures came to at 14 I answered your question
кому пришли твари в 14 я на ваш вопрос
now it's your turn to answer
ответил теперь ваша очередь отвечать
your turn to answer your turn I
ваша очередь отвечать ваша очередь
answer here  who ukraine came to what
отвечаю вот кто украина пришла в какую
country to kill people in mariupol what
страну убивать в мариуполе людей какую
setting
настройку
what country ukraine came to
какую страну пришла украина в мариуполь
mariupol at the age of 14 so call it  tsya
в 14 лет так это и называется
civil it was not some kind of DPR, that
гражданской это не было какой-то днр то
is, it was not the DPR, look at the one
есть это не было днр смотрите на тот
by sea where Ukraine came
по морю куда пришла украина это
from  from what date the dnr
с как а из какого с какой даты днр
exists which from which date diana
существует какого из какой даты diana
ross tell me from what date dn but
ross скажите с какой даты д н а
just from what date the dnr when the dnr was created
просто с какой даты днр когда создалась
tell me tell me when it was created because
днр скажите мне скажите когда создал из
of ours I understood this is not a dialogue
за нашим я понял не это не диалог потому
because you are just you just verbal diarrhea
что вы просто вы просто понос словесной
you  wear it and don’t want to answer
вы носите так и не хотите отвечать на
specific questions to specific questions
конкретные вопросы на конкретные вопросы
you can’t you tell me for 13 minutes what is
вы не может вы мне 13 минут расскажи что
not interesting to listen to but switch off if you are
не интересно слушать но отключитесь если
not interested
не интересно
if you are not interested yes then let’s
если вам не интересно да то давайте
tell you look when the
расскажем на смотрите когда создалась
Donetsk people’s republic was created
донецкая народная республика
if you are on fire on May 9 there  some
если вы горите 9 мая там какие-то
but to swim, and on the 11th there was a referendum on
а купаться а 11 числа был референдум 9
May 9, which means there was no Donetsk people's
мая значит не было донецкой народной
disk giving once to
дисковой давая раз к
yes, you see you are like you, you
да вот вы смотрите вы такие как вы вы
support these in  military actions in
поддерживаете вот эти военные действия в
ukraine russia you are a fool of yourself to
украине россии вы дурочку из себя
build this hat but you
строить этой шапочки одевает но вы
can’t listen to anything don’t smear so they
ничего не можете послушать не мажь так
chose you look at you you were
выбрали осмотри тебя тебя тебя была
like that looks that is you win
такой смотрит то есть вы выиграете можем
can you hear you interrupt
можете вы слышать вы перебиваете
interrupts because you are not half an hour 14
перебивает потому что вы не полчаса 14
years 45 days  you can’t name you, you’ll
лет 45 дней вы не можем назвать вы
do it in goodwill and dump
сделаете же в доброй воли и свалить
me, look, you won’t be able to get me out of the shop,
смотрите вы меня не сможете вывести шопа
I lay down, brother, and ran away, so
я лег братишка так и убежал так вот
let’s do everything for the Russians, this is what I
давайте для русских все вот это я так
love these people from Mariupol, who is
люблю этих людей из мариуполя который
somewhere in Rostov and a very demonstrative
где-то в ростове да очень показательный
patient
пациент
look, they all, they can’t speak
смотрите они все они не могут говорить
on facts at all, maybe they specifically
по фактам вообще могут они специально
want to switch to some kind of
хотят перейти на какие то там
insults in order to piss off the
оскорбления для того чтобы вывести
interlocutor and he began to freak out
собеседника из себя и он начал психовать
and then it already
и дальше это уже
went from some kind of emotional
переходил от какую--то эмоциональную
quarrel, like in a national quarrel there already
ссору как а в национальном ссоре там уже
there are no
нету
right ones, and there it’s already going to disk 100,
правых а там уже идет к диску 100 так
so this guy, yes, he’s sitting somewhere
вот этот парень да он сидит где-то там
on the stream, pouring a kite into his people, better
на стриме своим людям вливает кайт лучше
write, I find it for h  ert in the
напишите нахожу это за черт в
comments so we will find him we will get him
комментариях так найдем его достанем его
in height or where he sits there so at the
в роста или где он там сидит так вот в
age of 14 yes there are invaders up to 22 and he lived
14 года да там оккупанты до 22 и он жил
like he lived in Mariupol but for some reason
типа жил в мариуполе но почему-то его
these fascists the Nazis did not touch him but they
эти фашисты нацисты не трогали да вот
tortured him this cannot
всех пытали его такого не может
explain why he was not tortured and
объяснить почему его не пытали и вот эти
all these abstract torture yes we fell
все абстрактные пыточные да мы упали
abstract murder where let's list
абстрактные убийство где давайте список
those then the quasar was tortured on where to
тех тогда квазар запытали на где
see the list of those who were killed
посмотреть список список тех кого убили
in these torture mariupol i.e.
в этих пыточных мариуполя то есть
where the diet is all therefore they work
где диета все поэтому они работают по
according to these methodical ones so heap
вот этим методичным так наваливают
why  extract is funny why
почему экстракт смешно почему
ukraine occupied my attack
украина оккупировала моему приступ
mariupol of this part of ukraine how ukraine
мариуполь этой части украины как украина
can occupy its part they
может оккупировать свою часть они
juggle is understandable and why it
жонглируют понятен и почему у него
undermines him he doesn’t want to talk about the facts of
подрывает он не хочет говорить по фактам
whom he occupied so if he now
кого оккупировала так если он сейчас
says the dnr occupied because we will
скажет днр оккупировал так как мы
build from what moment there and how  the
встроим с какого момента там и как там
DPR appeared there no regional council
появилась днр никакой областной совет
Donetsk not Luhansk yes did not proclaim
донецкий не луганский да не провозглашал
any DPR elena
никакой днр елена
no mariup there  ole tikhan no one has ever
никакие там мариуполе тихан никто не пор
exalted any dnr there were some
возвышал никакой днр были некоторые
militants and before that seized
боевики и до которые захватили
certain buildings security forces
определенные здания силовые структуры
with the support of the russian
при поддержке российской
federation and they started doing outrages
федерации и они начали делать бесчинство
when there was this
когда в славян славянске был вот этот
shooter in slavyansk slavyansk on 12 april after he
стрелков даст 12 апреля после того как
was knocked out so these russian biku everything is
его выбили так этих российский бику все
fine  torso Slavic Crimea
нормально славянский крыму торс
I live normally and lived normally no
нормально живу и нормально жили никто
one no one no torture some murder
никого ни каких пыточных неких убийство
this is
это
Russian propaganda why why
российская пропаганда почему почему он
he can’t he can’t speak
не может он не может говорить по
essentially
существу
on doing everything himself funny he told me for 15
на делать все самому смешно он меня 15
minutes that it’s not
минут рассказывал что со мной не
interesting to talk to me because I can’t
интересно говорить потому что я не могу
to enter did, that is, if you
ввести делал то есть если ты
tell a person that you are not interested with him
говоришь человеку что с ним не интересно
, then why are you sitting if it would not be
так то почему сидишь если мне было бы не
interesting for me, I left such patients;
интересно я уходил мне такие пациенты
then it
начинает просто этом шапочку то он
happens to be a
бывает
cap of money, I will now start to shade
шапочка денег я сейчас начну тушеваться
or with music  here’s the museum,
или с музычкой вот музей они все
for some reason they all think that the year they have a
почему-то думают году у них-то министром
Rostov pre-trial detention center like there is a song about the basics
ростовское сизо типа там про азов песня
and here they are all including you don’t think I
на и вот они все включая ты не думаешь
’ll shorten the parts and you’ll start like
укорочу части включат и ты начнешь типа
there, God, they’ll turn it on, they’ll sell the
там боже короче они включили продаст
ovskaya season,
овская сезон
they can foist any song well  the meaning is,
любую песню могут всучить ну смысл так
that is, how it affects about me,
то есть как это влияет на примерно меня
well, listened well, go ahead and don’t
ну послушал хорошо давай дальше и не
get it and the type won’t stand it because
получает и тип не выдержит потому что
his whole strategy is designed for
вся его стратегия рассчитана на то что
you to fail and start it sends it
ты под гришь и начнешь его посылает она
awesome and like you see they are
офигенская а типа вот видите они там
dodik there but looks like a fool  he
додики но дурачком выглядит сам пачку
put on a pack optika took off .  bunches were born for
оделся optika снялся . родился пучки для
funny funny they are but we must
смешные смешные они но мы должны
understand that all this Russian
понимать что вся вот эта российская
propaganda was so it
пропаганда так она
went to ensure that
шла на то чтобы
more more people went to fight in
больше больше людей ехала воевать в
Ukraine because people were burned alive in
украину потому что людей заживо сожгли в
Odessa there a crucified boy was
одессе там распятый мальчик
bombed there an alley of angels in Gorlovskaya
разбомбили там аллея ангелы в горловской
madonna and so that is  Propaganda did all these things in
мадонна и так то есть все вот эти вещи
such a way in order
так пропаганда делала для того чтобы
to cling to a cool person in Russia,
цеплять за живое круто человека в россии
and he went to leave his guts in Ukraine
и он ехал оставлять свои кишки в украине
and killing people there, so it’s
так и убивая там людей поэтому
very good that now, on the other hand, a gesture of
очень хорошо что сейчас зато жест доброй
goodwill in Kharkov has already passed completely
воли в харькове прошла у них уже совсем
different, but
другие а
something  then they sprouts have already begun to
что-то они росточки уже начали себя по
behave differently and perceive nothing
другому вести и воспринимать ничего
Ukraine will liberate and Kherson region will liberate
украина освободит и херсонщина освободит
and
и
Zaporozhye region will liberate both Donetsk
запорожскую область освободит и донецкую
and Lugansk regions and Mariupol
и луганскую область и мариуполь
will be liberated by Rashists, although it was
освободят рашисты правда его
already bombed by
разбомбили уже
unsuitability on such a city, but the city will be
непригодности на такой но город будет
liberated, but such clowns from
освобожден а вот такие клоуны из ростова
Rostov will sit like this  they’re kidding donats there, and I’m
так будут сидеть они там кида донатики
making money on this that they
зарабатываю так и на этом что там
tease two Germans
дразнят двух немцев они
there, they exist in  from this worthless
существуют вот это свое никчемное
existence of
существование
ours, therefore, we must, in spite of that, you know,
поэтому мы должны несмотря на то знаете
this is how shelling is going on at the front, and the
вот как идет артобстрел на фронте так и
soldiers are holding on like that, we must
воины они держатся таким мы должны
hold on, they are pecking, they are calling us names,
держаться они там клюют они нас обзывают
they are turning on this music,
они там включают к этому музычку
we must keep an internal wound
мы должны держать внутренней рану весь
, this whole method is an attempt, but
вот этот метод попытка а
then we will keep them we will
потом мы с них будем держать мы будем
dance on the
танцевать еще на
grave of the russian federation so
могиле российской федерации так что
hang on subscribe put like in the
держитесь подписуйтесь ставте лайк в
crowd price telegram channel grazing
бове скопище цена телеграм-канал выпасе
tell that you respect still work with
передай что вы уважает еще работать с
his channel
его каналу доступ продуктивно и потрибно
office and
может и петр i mat один атом и в офисе и
do not forget to check and subscribe to youtube ink,
не забывайте проверять и подписку туши
which is very much where you sell a piece
youtube чему сильно где сбываете кусочку
directly to the property glory to Ukraine elections I smear
прямо имость слава украине выборы мажу
the clown workshop under saprykin's interest
цех клоуне под сапрыкин интерес